Asbel Fernandez

Information Technology

Hi, I am Asbel Fernandez. I am 35 years of age. I pursued a degree in Information Technology in the year of January 2020. I have basic knowledge in C++, Web Development and Windows Operating System. I have not had the opportunity to work in a team but I would appreciate forming part of one so that I can explore my skills and enhance my knowledge. I have ventured on research for personal projects, which have made me flexible to adapt to the advances of technology.

Experience

D*Victoria Hotel - Front Desk

June 2021-October 2022 Summary of Duties

- Greeting and Welcoming Guest
- Delivering all incoming and outgoing mail and packages
- Answering all calls and directing as needed

Bowen & Bowen LTD Warehouse assistant

March 2017–November 2018 Summary of duties:

- Receiving and processing incoming stock
- Picking and filling orders from stock
- Packing organizing and retrieving products

Independent Venture Network assistant

July 2018–September 2020: Summary of duties:

- Offered Troubleshooting Services
- Utilized TeamViewers to diagnose software issues

Coco Blanca Technical Assistant

May 2013–July 2014 Summary Duties:

Technical assistant on Basic Computer Software

Education

College

2018 – 2020: Graduated with a diploma in Information Technology from Centro Escolar Mexico Junior College

Highschool

2016 - 2018: Graduated from Corozal Community College (ACE)

Primary school

1994 – 2000: Graduated from La Inmaculada Roman Catholic School

Personal Information

Personal Strengths:

- Work well under pressure
- Responsible
- Honest
- Team Player
- Reliable
- Motivated
- Flexible

Languages spoken:

English/Spanish

Contact

PHONE: 607-2362

Email: asfer3031@gmail.com

References:

Name: Daniel Matu

Address: Orange Walk Town

Cell Number: 600-

6992

Name: Hugo Javier

Gonzalez

Address: Corozal

Town

Phone Number: 671-

7274

Email:

hgonzalez@cemjc.ed

<u>u.bz</u>